ties.com 2017-12-03

# Privacy Policy | Ties.com

At Ties.com we are committed to ensuring your privacy as a customer. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We are dedicated not only providing you, our customer, with the best possible shopping experience, but also to ensuring your complete privacy. Information we collect from you is used to process your orders with us and provide for you the best possible shopping experience. 

Ties.com is the sole owner of all personally identifiable information collected via our web site. By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy. 

### Information We Collect and the Uses For It

When you place an order with Ties.com we will need to know your full name, mailing address, e-mail address, phone number, credit card number, and credit card expiration date. This information is used to fulfill your order, including payment and shipping, and to notify you of your order status. 

To ship your order, it will be necessary for us to share your name, address, and telephone number with the shipping company of our choice. Shipping companies require this information to deliver your products. 

Upon completion of your order, your credit card information is deleted from our database to ensure your protection. 

We offer a free newsletter through Ties.com used to keep you informed of specials, deliver information of interest, and more. To sign up for the newsletter we will ask for your e-mail address. We will deliver the newsletter to your e-mail address, and you will have the option to stop your receipt of the publication at any time. We only require your e-mail address for the purpose of the newsletter, and you will only receive our newsletter if you so choose. 

We occasionally offer contests and special promotions on our site. In order to take part in these opportunities, we will need to gather your name, e-mail address, and mailing address. This information is used to notify winners and administer the specific contest or promotion. 

We may request your participation in online or offline surveys via e-mail, telephone, postal mail, or web pages. Surveys are strictly voluntary and your participation and/or answers do not prohibit or influence your use of our website. Furthermore, if you do participate in a survey, you may decline to answer any question, and all answers are held in strict confidence according to our privacy standards. Individually identifiable survey information is for the use of Ties.com only. General, aggregate survey results may be shared with third parties. Information you may be asked may include, but is not limited to, your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, income, age, gender, marital status, type of business, product usage, schooling, and hobbies. Survey data is used to enhance Ties.com to provide a better customer experience. 

When you make purchases at our site, we monitor the information enabling us to better serve you. We use the general purchasing information to help us determine what products and services you are most interested in. We also keep track of site traffic using log files to help us better determine what areas of our site are providing our customers with the greatest value. We use this information to fine tune our site and tailor it to you and other visitors to our site. 

From time to time we may use information we collect from you to notify you of important or exciting changes to our website, new or changing services we offer, and other special offers we think may be useful to you. If you decide you would rather not receive this information, send us an e-mail message and We'll take you off our mailing lists until you inform us otherwise. 

### Privacy Protection - How It's Done

The online shopping process at Ties.com is safe and secure. Whenever you are in the process of placing an order, accessing personal information, or providing personal information we use a secure server. Powerful, industry-standard SSL secure server software provides encryption for all information sent between your computer and ours. Additionally, we protect our server and all customer data against unauthorized use physically or electronically. 

### Cookies

The so-called cookie is a small piece of information that is stored on your computer's hard drive by your web browser and which may be accessed by our server. The cookies we provide to your browser do not contain any personal information, but they do allow us to provide special services to you while you visit our website. Cookies simplify the ordering process by remembering information about you, allow the use of the shopping cart function, and enable online ordering. 

If you do not wish to accept cookies, most browsers allow you to prevent them from being accepted and saved to your hard drive. If you choose not to use cookies, you will be unable to place online orders at our website. 

### Do Not Track Headers

Ties.com itself does not respond to the "Do Not Track" HTTP Header. 

### Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

Ties.com does not currently sell, trade, or rent your personal information to any third parties.

We may merge customer data stored in our database with data from third parties for the purposes of enhancing and marketing products and/or services to customers. 

We may provide aggregate statistics of our users to third parties in reference to traffic patterns, numbers of users, sales, and other site and customer information. This information will never provide any personally identifiable information on individual users. 

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

This refers to information that does not, by itself, identify you as a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based on where you have shopped for on our web site in several ways. This information is then compiled and analyzed on both an individual and an aggregate basis. Such non-personally identifiable information may include demographics and interest data. We use data from Google's Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender and interests) with Google Analytics. We use Google Analytics' Demographic and Interest Reporting Tools to figure out the general types of people who visit our store. Additional non-personally identifiable information may also include the Web site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") information as well as your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. A URL is the global address of documents and resources on the World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol ("TCP/IP") network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks use the TCP/IP protocol to route or reroute information based on the IP address of the destination. In other words, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, which allows web servers to locate and to identify your computer. Computers require an IP addresses in order for users to communicate over the Internet. 

### Notifying You of Changes to the Use of Your Information

If at some point in the future there is a change to our information usage practices that affects your personal information, we will post the relevant changes on our website. You should check this posted privacy statement periodically for changes. 

### Contacting You

We will send you e-mail messages during the processing of your order to verify your order placement and to notify you of its status. If there is a problem with your order, we may also contact you via e-mail, phone, or fax to notify you of the problem and solution. We may also contact you via e-mail, postal mail, phone, or fax regarding questions or comments you have regarding our website or our business. Surveys and post-sale satisfaction questions may also be administered via e-mail, postal mail, phone, or fax to help us better serve our customers. 

We also use your Personal Information (like your e-mail or postal address) to contact you with marketing and promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you (some of which may be sent by a third party service provider). If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or if you do not want us to share your Personal Information with these third party service providers, contact us at customerservice@ties.com with "Privacy" as the subject line of the e-mail. 

**Sending E-mails Via The Service**  
As part of the Service, Members may communicate with third parties through use of their Accounts. When a Member selects the option of adding one or more e-mail addresses to an online form, the message they create in the corresponding template will be sent from Wild Attire, Inc. to those e-mail addresses on their behalf. These e-mail addresses will be used only for the purpose of sending the e-mail communication to the addressee. 

### Contacting Us

You may contact us with any concerns you may have at 1 (800) 289-2843 or via e-mail at customerservice@ties.com. You may also send us correspondence via postal mail to the following address: 

Ties.com Customer Service  
10372 Stanford Ave, Suite Q  
Garden Grove, CA 92840 

### Summary

At Ties.com your privacy is one of our top priorities. We realize that your personal information is very important to you, just as you are very important to us. It is necessary for us to collect certain private information from you in order to make shopping at our site possible, however, we do not collect more information than is necessary nor do we use that information in ways other than what it was given to us for and the uses posted above. 

This Privacy Policy for Ties.com as stated herein is effective from July 1st, 2007.
